Hello everyone, today I will introduce to you how to make a drawstring on the inside of the waist.
Now our pants are finished.
Next, we need to add two drawstrings to the inside of the waist and waist of the waist to show the effect of the drawstring coming out of the hole and falling naturally from the inside out.
First of all, we look at the drawing window on the left and find the material.
Double click to open.
Next, find the drawstring and drawstring folder.
There are some related materials in the software.
Here we can choose the first drawstring file.
Right click to add it to the work area.
Next, we use the positioning ball tool to move it to a position closer to the window.
Then rotate it.
Move the top of the drawstring closer to the position of the hole in the window.
In order to avoid conflict, we can reactivate the virtual model first and hide the right click.
At the same time, we also freeze the entire pants.
Next, in the 2D window,
according to the mark on the panel,
the inner waist panel and the drawstring panel are sewed together.
Here we need to be careful not to reverse when sewing.
Here we can first let the part of the drawstring sewed together.
So we can use the fixing needle to fix the upper part first.
Then we can close it.
Next, in the 3D window,
right click to add the positioning ball tool.
Using the positioning ball tool,
we can move the part of the drawstring closer to the position of the hole in the window.
Then we can make a drawstring with an inward-outward rotation.
Next, we press Ctrl-W to remove the fix needle.
Press the control key to open the simulation.
Here the simulation will take some time.
You can wait patiently until it is stabilized.
Now our drawstring is sewn up.
We can activate the wheel.
Finally, we can adjust some details.
You can see that the position of the drawstring in the corner is not very natural.
The plate of the drawstring itself is relatively small.
We can change its particle diameter to 1.
Then we can re-model it.
Finally, we can also change the material and color of the drawstring and hook part.
After completion, remove all the holes in the plate and simulate to stabilize.
So, we have completed the production of a hook and hook inside drawstring.